itpaystoeatpasta.com 2016-03-16

# Privacy Policy - New World Pasta

### New World Pasta’s Privacy Statement

New World Pasta has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. Personal and demographic information gathered on this website remain confidential from any entities outside of New World Pasta and any New World Pasta affiliate with whom we have a Special Relationship as defined herein. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for New World Pasta.

### Information Automatically Logged

Your IP address is used to help us diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website and gather broad demographic information about our internet market.

### Cookies

Cookies are used to track login information and polling participation. No personal data is actually stored in cookies, only random strings that represent a user.

### Consumer Feedback and Response Forms

New World Pasta collects personally identifiable information primarily to respond to questions and comments, to e-mail updates, for notification of promotion winners and to send out information to subscribers. We may periodically request participation in surveys. Participation is purely voluntary.

### Surveys

From time to time, New World Pasta will conduct online surveys asking visitors for contact information such as email address and demographic information such as zip code, age, or income level. Contact information from the surveys is used to gather consumer and market information solely for use by New World Pasta.

### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. New World Pasta is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

### Special Relationships

All of the consumer-specific information gathered through this site is the sole property of New World Pasta. Any third parties that have a business relationship with New World Pasta have signed an agreement that they shall keep the New World Pasta Information strictly confidential and secret, and and shall not divulge, communicate or transmit the New World Pasta Information to any other parties and shall not use, employ or exploit the New World Pasta Information in any commercial manner without New World Pasta’s written consent.

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [webmaster@nwpasta.com](mailto:webmaster@nwpasta.com).
